<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ChatterBaby</string>

    <!--Name of pages-->

    <!--Questionnaire-->
    <string name="questionnaire_explanation">"         The secondary purpose of this study is to collect infant vocalizations to identify vocal patterns associated with autism and other neurodevelopmental disorders.
        \n
        Your questionnaire data will be stored in a secure HIPAA compliant server. You may also be given a followup survey(s) when your baby is older regarding whether your infant has been diagnosed with a neurodevelopmental disorder.
        "
    </string>

    <!--About Us-->
    <string name="about_us">"       The ChatterBaby project is led by Dr. Ariana Anderson along with the Code for the Mission Team: Lauren Dunlap (Android developer), Yining Zhao (iOS developer), Usha Nookala (signal processing), with additional support from the Computing Technologies Research Laboratory (CTRL), the Clinical and Translational Science Institute (CTSI), the Burroughs Wellcome Fund, and the Semel Institute for Neuroscience and Human Behavior at UCLA.
        \n
        We gratefully acknowledge the many contributions of Abeer Alwan, Delbert Whetter, Sanaz Whetter, Brianna Shaul, Susan Bookheimer, Mirella Dapretto, Don Vaughn, Carol Han, Mahtash Esfandiari, Sherry Eyer, Anne Jackson, UCLA Department of Statistics, UCLA Department of Electrical Engineering, and the OxVoc Team: Christine Parsons and Michelle Craske.</string>

    <!--FAQ2-->

    <!--Contact Info-->
    <string name="contact_info1">If you have any questions, comments or concerns about the research, you can talk to the one of the researchers. Please contact:
    </string>
    <string name="contact_info2">
        <b>Ariana Anderson, Ph.D. \n
        University of California, Los Angeles \n
        Department of Psychiatry and Biobehavioral Sciences</b> \n
        760 Westwood Plaza, Ste C8-734 \n
        Los Angeles, CA 90095-1406 \n
        ariana82@ucla.edu \n
        (213) 973-7465 \n
    </string>
    <string name="contact_info3">If you have questions about your rights while taking part in this study, or you have concerns or suggestions and you want to talk to someone other than the researchers about the study, please call the OHRPP at (310) 825-7122 or write to:
    </string>
    <string name="contact_info4">
        <b>UCLA Office of the Human Research Protection Program (OHRPP)</b> \n
        11000 Kinross Avenue \n
        Suite 211, Box 951694 \n
        Los Angeles, CA 90095-1694</string>

    <!--EULA-->
    <string name="accept">OK</string>
    <string name="title_activity_why_cry_visualization">Visualization</string>
    <string name="title_activity_questionnaire">Questionnaire</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="title_activity_register_email">Register Email</string>
    <string name="title_activity_faq">FAQ</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="whyCryText">Hungry, fussy, or in pain?</string>
    <string name="isCryText">Is baby crying?</string>
    <string name="isPainText">Is baby in pain?</string>


</resources>
