<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Chatterbaby</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_message"></string>

    <!--Questionnaire-->
    <string name="questionnaire">Questionnaire</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_explanation">"         The secondary purpose of this study is to collect infant vocalizations to identify vocal patterns associated with autism and other neurodevelopmental disorders.
        Your questionnaire data will be stored in a secure HIPAA compliant server. You may also be given a followup survey(s) when your baby is older regarding whether your infant has been diagnosed with a neurodevelopmental disorder."
    </string>

    <!--About Us-->
    <string name="about_us_title">About Us</string>
    <string name="about_us">This project is led by Dr. Ariana Anderson, research faculty in the
        Department of Psychiatry at UCLA, and Don Vaughn, a neuroscience graduate student. The
        investigators have donated their time to create the mathematical predictive models.
        Although a beta-version is complete, further work and funding is needed to refine this
        sound-interpretation technology.
        \n\n
        Android development: Lauren Dunlap
        \n\n
        Collaborators:
        \n\n
        Usha Amrutha Nookala and Yining Zhao
        UCLA Computer Technologies Research Lab
        UCLA Clinical and Translational Science Institute.
        UCLA Department of Psychiatry and Biobehavioral Sciences
        UCLA Department of Statistics
        Burroughs Wellcome Fund
        Malibu Methodist Nursery School
        \n\n
        The research described was supported by NIH/National Center for Advancing Translational
        Science (NCATS) UCLA CTSI Grant Number UL1TR000124.</string>

    <!--Contact Info-->
    <string name="contact_title"> Contact Us </string>
    <string name="contact_info">• If you have any questions, comments or concerns about the research, you can talk to the one of the researchers. Please contact:
        \n\n
        \t Ariana Anderson, Ph.D. \n
        \t University of California, Los Angeles \n
        \t Department of Psychiatry and Biobehavioral Sciences \n
        \t 760 Westwood Plaza, Ste C8-734 \n
        \t Los Angeles, CA \n
        \t 90095-1406 \n
        \t ariana82@ucla.edu \n
        \t (310) 254-5680 \n
        \n
        • If you have questions about your rights while taking part in this study, or you have concerns or suggestions and you want to talk to someone other than the researchers about the study, please call the OHRPP at (310) 825-7122 or write to:
        \n\n
        \t UCLA Office of the Human Research Protection Program (OHRPP) \n
        \t 11000 Kinross Avenue, Suite 211, Box 951694 \n
        \t Los Angeles, CA 90095-1694</string>

    <!--EULA-->
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="eula_string">

        UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA LOS ANGELES
        STUDY INFORMATION SHEET
        \n\n
        Visualization of Infant Vocalizations for Hearing Impaired Parents
        \n\n
        Dr. Ariana Anderson from Department of Psychiatry and Biobehavioral Sciences at the University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) is conducting a research study.
        You were selected as a possible participant in this study because you are responsible for a child. Your participation in this research study is voluntary.
        \n\n
        • Why is this study being done?
        "The purpose of the study is to create a baby monitor smart-phone app for hearing impaired parents, which will allow infant vocalizations to be transmitted and "translated" into both a visualization modality and labeled states on the smart-phone of hearing impaired parents. The study may help us understand how infant vocalizations change over time and with different needs, and how to visually "translate" this information so that a hearing-impaired parent may interpret a child's vocal cues."
        The secondary purpose of this study is to collect infant vocalizations to identify vocal patterns associated with autism and other neurodevelopmental disorders. Your uploaded audio samples will be stored in a secure HIPAA compliant server along with your Infant History Questionnaire. You may also be given a followup survey(s) when your baby is older regarding whether your infant has been diagnosed with a neurodevelopmental disorder.
        \n\n
        • What will happen if I take part in this research study?
        If you volunteer to participate in this study, the researcher will ask you to do the following:
        \n
        \n • Take audio recordings of your child
        \n • "Record your perception of your child's mood state"
        \n • "Fill out questionnaires regarding your infant's developmental history and family background."
        \n\n
        \n • Whatever decision you make, there will be no penalty to you, and no loss of benefits to which you were otherwise entitled.
        \n • You may refuse to answer any questions that you do not want to answer and still remain in the study.
        \n\n
        » Who can I contact if I have questions about this study?
        \n\n • The research team:
        If you have any questions, comments or concerns about the research, you can talk to the one of the researchers. Please contact:
        \n\n
        Ariana Anderson, Ph.D.
        University of California, Los Angeles
        Department of Psychiatry and Biobehavioral Sciences
        760 Westwood Plaza, Ste C8-734
        Los Angeles, CA
        90095-1406
        ariana82@ucla.edu
        (310) 254-5680
        \n\n
        • UCLA Office of the Human Research Protection Program (OHRPP):
        If you have questions about your rights while taking part in this study, or you have concerns or suggestions and you want to talk to someone other than the researchers about the study, please call the OHRPP at (310) 825-7122 or write to:
        \n\n
        UCLA Office of the Human Research Protection Program
        11000 Kinross Avenue, Suite 211, Box 951694
        Los Angeles, CA 90095-1694
        \n\n
        By clicking "Accept" you are providing your digital signature, indicating your informed consent to participate in this research study."

    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_why_cry">WhyCryActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_no_cry">NoCry</string>
    <string name="title_activity_why_cry_visualization">WhyCryVisualization</string>
    <string name="title_activity_no_pain">NoPainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us">AboutUsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact">ContactActivity</string>
</resources>
